

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

□ (415)203-8543 | ☑ chi45@purdue.edu | ♠ hyung-gun.me | □ stnoah1 | □ hyung-gun | ➢ Hyung-gun Chi

# Research Interests

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning and Temporal Action Anaylsis. In this area, I apply Machine/Deep Learning algorithms for Augmented/Virtual Reality and Smart Factory.

# **Education**

**Purdue University** 

West Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT

· Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

**Yonsei University** 

Seoul, South Korea

• Advisor: Professor Soo-Hong Lee

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

· 2011-2013, 2-year military service

Skills

Language Python, Matlab, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Machine/Deep Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow, Keras

**Web Programming** MYSQL/mongoDB, Flask/Node.js

CAD Tool Creo Parametric, SolidWorks, AutoCAD

ETC GAZEBO, ROS

# **Publications and Patents**

#### **Conference Proceedings**

- [C2] H. G. Chi, S. Kim, X. Hu, O. Huang, and Karthik Ramani. A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020, accepted.
- [C1] S. Kim, H. G. Chi, and Karthik Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020, accepted.

#### **Journal Papers**

- [J3] S. Kim, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design, 2020, accepted.
- [J2] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. G. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In The Visual Computer, pp. 1-15, 2019
- [J1] H. T. Hwang, H. G. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST), 33(3), pp. 1333-1339, 2019

#### **Patents**

• [P1][PDF] H. G. Chi. Computer Input Automation System. KR Patent (2017): 10-1745330.

# **Working Experience**

#### **Software Engineer and CEO**

Seoul, South Korea

**NEIL LAB CORPORATION** 

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

- Found and lead a start-up company as a CEO and Software Engineer. The company was funded \$ 30,000 by the SeongNam Industry Promotion Agency.
- Develop an office automation system specifically for automating office tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts.
- · Designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically scrap and integrate customer's financial and personal data. (Relevant patent: [P1])

### **Mechanic and Squad leader**

Inje, South Korea

Apr. 2011 - Jan. 2013

REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY

- Maintain military weapons and equipment including firearms and vehicles.
- Lead a squad as a squad leader; honored as a distinguished soldier.